Curriculum Vitae

Name: Mr. Sunthorn Srirang

Age : 39 Years Date of Birth : 12 Sep 1981

Sex : Male Health : Excellent

Weight: 85 kg Height: 183 cm.

Marital Status: Married Place of Birth: Songkhla Province (Thailand)

Nationality: Thai Race: Thai Religion: Buddhism

Military Service () Exempted () Military (/) Discharged

Address No.: 77/345 Moo 17 Bueng Kham Phroi, Lamlukka, Pathumthani, 12150, Thailand

Mobile no.: +6686-7832374

Email: peebaowjoy@gmail.com

Summary

Over 15 years of experience in QA/QC inspector for inspection, verification and expediting work of structure, piping, mechanical (static equipment: vessel, tower, heat exchanger, tank, stack, reactors and rotating installation work such as pump equipment) in Petrochemical, and also structural, piping, equipment for module platform fabrication/installation in Oil & Gas field with various applicable code/standard such as ASTM, API,ASME, AWS, EN, Norsok, ABS, DNV.

Inspection and control work at fabricate shop due to construction and installation at yard. Monitoring and control for all NDT activity and interpret of RT film, Progress report, Hydrostatic test, Pneumatic test, Monitoring inspection of material Identification traceability, fit –up check of weld joint preparation and welding process. Witness welding qualification (WPQR's/Welder qualification test), Clarify WPS/PQR and Approved, visual and dimension inspection. Painting inspection, packing inspection.

Educational Background:

Bachelor of Industrial Technology (Welding Technology), King Mongkut's Institute of Technology North Bangkok

Training Courses:

- ➤ Certificate Ultrasonic testing Level II, Accordance with ASNT' SNT TC 1A
- ➤ Certificate Radiographic testing Level II, Accordance with ASNT' SNT TC 1A
- ➤ Certificate Magnetic particle testing Level II, Accordance with ASNT' SNT TC 1A
- ➤ Certificate Liquid Penetrant Testing Level II, Accordance with ASNT' SNT TC 1A
- CWI AWS QC1, AWS Certification of Welding Inspector



Professional Experience:

Date : 2019 - Present

Employer: TTCL Public Company Limited.

Role : Welding Inspector

Description

The following scope of Inspection was carried out in accordance with the Inspection and Test plan and found to comply with the specification. Visual and fit-up and dimension inspections of piping fabrication and Installation, storage tank fabrication and Installation, Double wall tank fabrication and Installation. Inspection Hydrostatic test and Pneumatic test, interprets of RT film due to review NDT Report, MDR and package of piping. Review and endorsement of material mill certificate, Clarify WPS/PQR and Approved, clarify permit to work for activity.

Project Experience:

Owner's : PTT GLOBAL CHEMICAL (GC)

Project : ORP PROJECT (D-189)

Main Contractor : TTCL Public Company Limited

Title : Welding Inspector

Date : 2018 - 2019

Employer: TTCL Public Company Limited.

Role : QC Supervisor

Description:

The following scope of Inspection was carried out in accordance with the Inspection and Test plan and found to comply with the specification. Visual and dimension inspections of storage tank fabrication and Installation. Inspection Hydrostatic test and Pneumatic test for storage tank, interpret of RT film due to review MDR storage tank. Inspections weld joint preparation and welding process for piping. Visual and dimension inspections of piping fabrication and Installation, clarify package history sheet and interpret of RT film of piping. Inspection and preparation hydrostatic test, pneumatic test for of piping.

Project Experience:

Owner's : THAI MMA CO.,LTD

Project : MMA PROJECT (D-187)

Main Contractor: TTCL Public Company Limited

Title : QC Supervisor

Date : Aug 2017-2018

Employer: TTCL Public Company Limited.

Role : QC Supervisor

Description:

The following scope of Inspection was carried out in accordance with the Inspection and Test plan and found to comply with the specification. Inspections weld joint preparation and welding process. Visual and dimension inspections of piping fabrication and Installation, Clarify package history sheet of piping. Inspection Hydrostatic test and Pneumatic test for piping.

Project Experience:

Owner's : PTT GLOBAL CHEMICAL

Project : LLDPE EXPANSION AND HEXENE-1 PROJECT (D-184)

Main Contractor : TTCL Public Company Limited

Title : QC Supervisor

Date : Sep 2016 - 2017

Employer: TTCL Public Company Limited.

Role : QC Inspector

Description:

The following scope of Inspection was carried out in accordance with the Inspection and Test plan and found to comply with the specification. Review and endorsement of material mill certificate, WPS/PQR and WQT, NDE reports (PAUT, RT, UT, UTM, PT, and MT) PWHT Report, Hardness Report, PMI Report, Hydrostatic test reports, Pneumatic test report, Monitoring of material Identification traceability, Weld joint preparation and welding process. Visual and dimension inspections of piping fabrication and Installation, Monitoring Inspections the Equipment modify. Clarify package history sheet of piping, Due to Clarify package of Equipment modify.

Project Experience:

Owner's : SCG/ROC

Project : ROCD Project / D-183 (Shutdown Turnaround)

Main Contractor : TTCL Public Company Limited

Fabricator : SKC, UNIMIT

Title : QC Inspector

Date : 2011 – Aug 2016

Employer: DNV-GL (Thailand) Ltd.

Role : Welding Inspector

Description:

The following scope of Inspection was carried out in accordance with the Inspection and Test plan and found to comply with the specification. Review and endorsement of material mill certificate, WPS/PQR and WQT, NDE reports (RT, UT, UTM, PT, MT), Progress report, Hydrostatic test reports, Pneumatic test report, Monitoring of material Identification traceability, fit –up check of weld joint preparation and welding process. Witness of mechanical test for Production welds, Base metal and PQR, Visual and dimension inspection. Painting inspection as well as packing inspection before delivery.

Project Experience:

Owner's : Petrobas

Project : Petrobas P74

Main Contractor : Aibel Thailand Limited

Fabricator : Deeline

Title : Welding Inspector (DNV Verification work)

Equipment : P74 Module fabrication/installation for 5 Modules

(M01, M08, M09, M14 & M15)

Owner's : TPK Ethanol Company Limited.

Project: TPK ETHANOL 340,000 LITRES/DAY x 3 PLANT PROJECT

Fabricator : Sutech Manufacturing Company Limited.

Title : Welding Inspector (Representative of TPK)

Equipment : Pressure Vessels, Tanks, Towers & Heat exchanger

Date : 2010 – 2011

Employer: AIBEL THAILAND COMPANY LTD.

Role : QA/QC Engineer

Description:

Monitoring welding inspections of piping fabrication and installation due to control and plan NDT activity and interpret of RT films. Review NDT report (RT, UT Phased array, PT & MT) Review and approved hydrostatic test report (piping package)

Project Experience:

Owner : MODEC

Project: TUPI Petrobras FPSO Cidade de Angra dos Reis MV22

Equipment : Floating Production, Storage and Offloading (FPSO)

Date : 2009 - 2010

Employer: TOYO-THAI CORPORATION PUBLIC COMPANY LTD.

Role : QC Inspector

Description:

The following scope of Inspection was carried out in accordance with the Inspection and Test plan and found to comply with the specification. Review and endorsement of material mill certificate, WPS/PQR and WQT, NDE reports (RT, UT, UTM, PT, MT), Progress report, Hydrostatic test reports, Pneumatic test report, Monitoring of material Identification traceability, fit –up check of weld joint preparation and welding process. Witness of mechanical test for Production welds, Base metal and PQR, Visual and dimension inspection. Painting inspection as well as packing inspection before delivery.

Project Experience:

Owner : PTT Phenol Company Limited.

Project : PPCL BPA PROJECT

Equipment : Pressure Vessels, Tanks, Towers & Reactors

Date : 2006-2008

Employer: DEE-LINE CONSTRUCTION COMPANY LTD.

Role : Welding Engineer & QA/QC Engineer

Description:

Monitoring and quality control for welding work during production period (including WPS & PQR & WQT) such as Preheat/PWHT requirement, correct welding electrodes, visual inspection before NDT and NDT work. Control and Issue Test Inspection Request (TIR) to all concerned party and make sure internal inspection was performed. Monitoring/control the ITP activity as well as any special requirement that related to project specification & code/standard.

Working Experience:

Module (Structure & Piping & Pressure Vessel)

Project name : Vincent FPSO Project.

Owner : MAERSK CONTRACTORS

Customer : Aibel Company Ltd. Rayong.

Position : Welding Engineer & QA/QC Engineer

Type of Work : FLOATING PRODUCTION, STORAGE & OFF LOADING

Total : 4 Module 4500 tons

Project name : Aker Smart1 Project.

Owner : AKER FLOATING PRODUCTION

Customer : Aibel Company Ltd. Rayong.

Position : Welding Engineer & QA/QC Engineer

Type of Work : FLOATING PRODUCTION, STORAGE & OFF LOADING Total

Total : 4 Module 1350 tons

Project name : ETTRICK FPSO/ LER.CONTAINER

Owner : MAERSK CONTRACTORS

Customer : Aibel Company Ltd. Rayong.

Position : Welding Engineer & QA/QC Engineer

Type of Work : FLOATING PRODUCTION, STORAGE & OFF LOADING

Project name : CIDADE DE SAO METEUS

Owner : PROSAFE (SINGAPORE)

Customer : Aibel Company Ltd. Rayong.

Position : Welding Engineer & QA/QC Engineer

Type of Work : FLOATING PRODUCTION, STORAGE & OFF LOADING

Total : 5 Module 1400 tons

Project name : MODIFY WHRU STACK PROJECT

Owner : PTT Public Company Limited. (Rayong)

Customer : PATKOL PUBLIC CO., LTD.

Position : Welding Engineer & QA/QC Engineer

Type of Work : Modify WHRU STACK, Gas separations plant # 5

Total : 700 tons. High 135 m.

Reference Person:

Mr. Thongsuk Pipatnawakit, Technical Manager, DNV-GL Tel. 084-4599441

Mr. Direk Hannarong, QA/QC Manager, Aibel Thailand Ltd. Tel. 081-9305197

Mr. Manit Jimlimlert, Manager, Dee line Construction Company ltd. Tel. 081-845-7320

Mr. Somboonkit Chaiwong, CHIEF QC D-183, TTCL Public Company Ltd. Tel. 092-7358338

Mr Sattawat A. CHIEF QC D-184, TTCL Public Company Ltd. Tel. 088-0154410

Mr. Chaiwat A. CHIEF QC D-187, TTCL Public Company Ltd. Tel. 081-9251176

Mr. Tunwa S. CHIEF QC D-189, TTCL Public Company Ltd. Tel. 084-6505154